<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Boot animation Chooser</string>
    <string name="main_head">Boot animation Chooser</string>
    <string name="bootanimation_reset_title">Reset</string>
    <string name="bootanimation_reset_summary">Reset a Boota nimation</string>
    <string name="bootanimation_preview_title">Preview</string>
    <string name="bootanimation_preview_summary">Preview A Boot animation</string>
    <string name="bootanimation_title">Choose</string>
    <string name="bootanimation_summary">Choose a Boot animation</string>
    <string name="remove_ui">Reset to default.</string>
    <string name="move_ui">Successfully set Boot animation</string>
    <string name="install_bootnim_title">Install</string>
    
    <string name="start_message">
    Thank you for choosing Boot Animation Chooser. There is some required information on how to setup 
    and run this application properly found below
    \n\n
    Below you will notice two installation methods. The recommended option being the binary installer, 
    however this unfortunately does not work on every device. If you know for sure this method does 
    not work on your device please choose the alternate installation method, this will work on all 
    devices. Don\'t worry if you\'re unsure, this is changeable in the preferences menu later.
    \n\n
    If you chose the binary installation method and it did not work for you, you can click \"Uninstall\" 
    and this will remove the binary and then you can go into the preferences and choose the alternate 
    method for installing Boot animations.
    \n\n
    In order to set your Boot Animation you will want to slide your finger to the left, accessing the
    File Chooser on the right hand side. You will want to choose the boot animation zip file that
    is located on your SD card. If you do not have one yet, you can download a boot animation from the
    internet and then connect your device to your computer and move the boot animation file over to your
    SD card.
    \n\n
    Once you have chosen a boot animation you can slide back to the Main view where you can \"Preview\"
    the chosen or current animation. Once you\'re pleased with your choice you can choose \"Set Chosen File\".
    This will set the boot animation for you.
    </string>
</resources>
